A mystical passage to Adventure
Search for the Jewel of Polaris: Mysterious Museum is a
fantasy, family film directed by David Schmoeller.
While visiting a museum, two siblings Ben and Kim a fierce electrical storm creates
a passage between the real world and worlds within the paintings.
They are magically whisked through time to the 1600's and find they must square off against a
wicked magician and also locate a valuable jewel in order to return to the present day.
Ben, played by A.J. Trauth.
Kim, played by Brianna Brown.
Casey, played by Megan Lusk.
Palmay, played by Michael Lee Gogin.
Monty, played by John Duerler.
Falco, played by Adrian Neil.
This is a list of all films produced by Full Moon Features.
Note that this does not include any films that were produced by Charles Band prior to the creation
of Full Moon, even though Full Moon now distributes some of them, such as Trancers.
For a list of these pre-Full Moon productions, see Empire Pictures filmography.
The film explores themes of lightning, painting, jewel, medieval, art museum.